One area that AWS networking differs
AWS 网络不同的一个区域
from a traditional network is in debugging network traffic.
来自传统网络正在调试网络流量
On a traditional network,
在传统网络上
you could use a packet sniffer to examine the traffic flowing across your network.
您可以使用包嗅探器来检查流经网络的流量
Because of the layers of virtualization that all of the AWS network is built on,
由于所有构建 AWS 网络的虚拟化层
and for security reasons,
出于安全考虑
you are not allowed to examine packets as freely.
不允许您随意检查包
AWS has tools and services that aid in the network debugging.
AWS 具有用于帮助网络调试的工具和服务
VPC Flow logs show you information about
VPC 流日志显示有关
network flows which includes the source and destination of a particular traffic flow,
包括特定业务流的源和目的地的网络流
but not the packets themselves.
但包裹本身并不是
Traffic Mirroring is a recent feature,
" 流量镜像 " 是最近的一个功能部件
but it does allow for packets inspection,
但它能让信息包检查
but it's not quite as simple as putting a network interface into promiscuous mode.
但这并不像把网络接口变成混杂模式那么简单